

### **Personal**

Names Innocent Emanuel Hlongwane

**Date of Birth** 04-11-1996

**Address** 

3181 Ext 6 Tswelepele 1632 Tembisa

**Phone Number** 076 253 8318

Email innocent38318@gmail.com

Driver's license: C10

## **Interests**

Travelling Reading Programming

Researching

# **Innocent Emanuel Hlongwane**

I am problem solver, reliable and capable candidate with limited experience in Front-end and Back-end Development. Graduated at TUT in position of National Diploma in IT(Software Development) as well as EON certificate VR and AR application development. I am a confident developer and positive that I can add value to company.

# **Work experience**

#### **Database Developer**

## **Terra Analytics**

Current

Create and maintaining database structures, making sure data is stored efficient using SQL queries, procedures and functions

# Front-end developer Jthoka & Co

Freelancer

Developing responsive website, Developing UI/UX for web Applications Using Figma, HTML5, CSS, Ajax, Jquery, Java Script, PHP Web Hosting

-----

# **Web** Developer

Freelancer

2019-2021

Developing websites for companies and personal website usingWordpress and( javascript, jqueries , html5, css)

Full Stack web developer using (php, javascript, jqueries , html5, css, sql)

Maintaining Web Application life Cycle.

Creating JSON API.

Monitoring the Web Server performance.

------

#### **VR and AR Developer**

Tshwane IDC(EON Reality), Pretoria West. 2019-2020

\_\_\_\_\_

Creating 3D objects and adding animations using 3Ds Max.

Adding Graphics to the objects using Photoshop.

Creating VR & AR Applications using unity and EON Studio.

Back-end Developer using C# and javaScript.

# **Skills**

Database Design.

Application Development.

Business Analysis and modeling.

Computer literacy: MS Package competent and Linux basics. Installation (Windows Operating System (xp,7,vistar,8,10)
Communication Skill.
Programming.
Team player.
Work well under pressure and meet deadlines.
Managing System Components.

### **Education**

National Diploma in Software

DevelopmentTshwane university of

Technology

January 2015 – December 2019

#### modules Covered

System Software (A+, N+, Linux Command),

Managing System Components,

Network (CISCO),

Technical Programming (C++),

Development Software (SQL, PL SQL)

Information Systems (Database, UML, Project Management)

Support Services (OS, GUI, Html, JS, CSS)

#### **Skill matrix**

Technology skills	Y/M of Experience	Last used	Rating
Bootstrap	3 Years	Current	4
C++	2 Years	2019	3
C#	1 Year	2019	2
Css	4 Years	Current	5
HTML5	4 Years	Current	5
Javascript	3 Years	Current	4
Php	3 Years	Current	4
Photoshop	1 Year	2019	2
PL/SQL	1 Year	2018	2
SQL	3 Years	Current	4
Wordpress	1 Year	Current	3

Level	Proficiency
1	Course/Training only
2	Limited Practice Experience
3	Solid Practice Experience
4	Well versed, Extensive Experience
5	Expert Level

# <u>Reference</u>

Miss Sebothoma B Coordinator/Supervisor 079 757 4779 Tshwane IDC

Tshwane university of Technology

Mr Ranko VN Lecturer / WIL Coordinator 012-382 9112/ 9938 Mr Thola J

Jthoka & Co

CEO 072 546 8575